[
  {
    "question": "In HTML, you can embed SVG elements directly into an HTML page",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "There is no concept of pointers in Java",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "C++ is purely object oriented programming language",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "False",
    "id": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "You can chain comparison in python",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The name python is about snakes",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "False",
    "id": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "Java was called Oak at the beginning",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "The first ever Linux kernel just occupied  65 MB",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "False",
    "id": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "Many programming languages are influenced by c++, some of which include C#, Java and even newer versions of C",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "In python you cannot return multiple values in a function",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "False",
    "id": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "All of the 500 fastest supercomputers run Linux",
    "opt1": "True",
    "opt2": "False",
    "ans": "True",
    "id": 10
  }
]